我是奧利弗•奎恩
My name is Oliver Queen.
五年裡  我被困在地獄一般的小島上
After five years on a hellish island,
我回來只有一個目標
I have come home with only one goal--
拯救我的城市
To save my city.
但要達到目標  我不能像過去一樣成為兇手
But to do so, I can't be the killer I once was.
為了紀念我的朋友  我只能偽裝成另一個人
To honor my friend's memory, I must be someone else.
深切懷念托馬斯•梅林
孝子
成為另一個存在
I must be something else.
《綠箭俠》前情回顧
Previously on "Arrow"...
我在阿富汗的時候  我的部隊的任務
When I was in Afghanistan,, my unit was tasked
是保護葛雷姆•卡迪爾
with protecting Gholem Qadir.
販賣鴉片  販賣兒童
Sold opium. Sold children.
你覺得你哥哥是怎麼死的
How is it you think your brother ended up dead?
你向一名客戶開槍  但是打偏了
You shot at a client, you missed.
我從不會打偏
I don't miss.
你殺了莎朵
You murdered Shado.
是的  扳機是我扣動的
Yes, I pulled the trigger,
但是你  槍口是你瞄準的
but you, you aimed the gun.
你在這裡幹什麼
What are you doing here?
五年前  我對你做出過一項承諾
Five years ago, I made you a promise.
我不會讓你死  直到你瞭解什麼叫徹底絕望
You cannot die until you have known complete despair.
你會瞭解的  我向你承諾
And you will. I promise.
莎拉
Sara.
Sara?
兇手
Murderer.
[俄語]
你好嗎  我的朋友
我能幫你什麼
What can I do for you?
星城可沒有古拉格監獄
There's no Gulags here in Starling City.
阿納托利話太多
Anatoly talks too much.
是啊
Eto verno.
我需要你幫我找一個人
I need you to find a man for me.
他名叫斯萊德•威爾遜  是個有錢的澳大利亞人
His name is Slade Wilson. He's rich, Australian,
一隻眼睛瞎了
and he's missing an eye.
我得知道他睡在哪裡
I need to know where he sleeps.
首先  我需要你幫我的忙
First, I need your assistance with my business.
有個人欠我很大一筆錢
There is a man who owes me a substantial amount of money.
我不是來交易的
I am not here to trade.
你知道我們的友情是什麼回事
You know how our brotherhood works.
我幫你一個忙
I do a favor for you
你也幫我一個忙
and you do one for me.
記在我賬上  阿列克西
Put it on my tab, Aleksi.
我沒時間玩這些遊戲
I don't have time for these games.
那就騰出時間
Make time.
除非你對我有用
My services are of no use to you
否則我不對你提供幫助
unless yours are use to me.
好吧
Ok.
我知道這種友情是怎麼回事
I know exactly how this brotherhood works,
現在  你為我服務
And right now, it works for me.
明白了嗎
綠   箭   俠
第二季 第十六集
我醒來時你已經走了
I woke up and you were gone.
我不累
Yeah. I wasn't tired.
你該累的
You should be.
你上次睡覺是什麼時候
When's the last time you actually slept?
在我發現斯萊德•威爾遜還活著之前
Right before I found out that Slade Wilson is still alive.
你想談談嗎
Do you want to talk?
我是說
I mean...
我知道我倆都
I know neither one of us
不大擅長分享感情
are very good about sharing our feelings,
但是我明白
but...I mean, I get it.
斯萊德  還有...
Slade, and...
事情很多
And it's a lot, and, you know,
如果你害怕也沒關係  我也是
it's ok if you're scared. I am, too.
我不怕
I'm not scared.
斯萊德回星城是有計劃的
Slade came back to Starling City with an agenda.
首先  他想大量生產米拉庫魯
First, he tries to mass produce the Mirakuru.
然後他出現在
Then he shows up...
我母親的家裡
at my mother's house.
他想爭鬥  沒問題
So he wants a fight, fine.
我滿足他  這次
I'll give him a fight. And this time,
我殺了他時
when I kill him,
會保證他死得透透的
I will make damn sure that he stays dead.
我只是得找到他
I just need to find him.
咖啡嗎
Coffee?
熱可哥
Hot cocoa.
沒有棉花糖嗎
What, no marshmallows?
沒有了
I'm out.
你在這裡做什麼  狄格
What are you doing here, Dig?
留神一切
Keeping an eye on things.
好吧  你說的一切指的是我的脖子吧
Ok. And by things, you mean my neck.
你覺得斯萊德•威爾遜會趁我睡著時扭斷它
The one you think Slade Wilson's going to break in my sleep.
是啊  類似吧
Yeah, something like that.
我派遣了額外保安保護奧利弗的媽媽
Look, I have extra security details on Oliver's mother.
羅伊照看著西婭
Roy's keeping an eye on Thea,
莎拉和勞蕾爾在一起
Sara's staying close to Laurel.
所以我攤上了你  坐在我家門外
So I get you sitting outside of my house
就像大一那個曲棍球隊員一樣
like that lacrosse player my freshman year of college.
在遇見你和奧利弗之前  我有生活的
You know, I had a life before you and oliver, yeah?
好吧  我只想確保你沒事  費利西蒂
Right. I just want to make sure you're ok, Felicity.
我很喜歡你這樣
And I love you for it.
但如果斯萊德想殺了我  他就能做到
But if Slade wants to kill me, he can.
你無法阻止他
There's nothing you can do to stop him.
回家去  好嗎
So go home. Ok?
睡衣蠻好看
Nice jammies.
奧斯特蘭德酒店
1141房間  馬上來
怎麼這麼久才來
What took you so long?
這是搞什麼
What is all this?
現在喝香檳有點早  不是嗎
A little early for champagne, don't you think?
我不覺得
Not for me.
我剛從平壤執行完任務
I just got back from a mission in Pyongyang.
該死
Well, damn.
是你啊
That was you?
對不起  那是機密信息
I'm sorry. That's classified information.
但我想念我的前夫  新男友
But I missed my ex-husband, new boyfriend.
超能聯合調查組在這個酒店
And A.R.G.U.S. has a standing reservation
給重要人物留了一個長久房
at this hotel for very important assets.
你能留下來嗎
Can you stay?
奧利弗和我遇上了...
Well, Oliver and I kind of have a...
一點事
situation.
一切都沒事吧
Everything all right?
是啊  我們在處理
Yeah, yeah, we're handling it.
就是說能留下來
So you can stay.
阿富汗  坎達哈  南區指揮部
有什麼問題嗎  麥考斯
Is there a problem, Michaels?
六年前
我們需要休息  女人們都累了
We need to rest. These women are tired.
我們都累了
We're all tired.
距離營地還有很長的路  繼續走
It's a long hike back to camp. Keep going.
要我去向女人們解釋
Shall I go explain to the
需要在天黑前回去的原因嗎
ladies why they want to get back before dark?
她們不能和你說話
They're not allowed to talk to you.
為什麼  因為我是個美國人嗎
Why, 'cause I'm an American?
因為你是個男人
Because you're a man.
休息五分鐘吧
Five minutes.
女人參軍  不能挺
Girls in the military. Can't keep up,
就別進  這話真沒錯
don't join up, right?
你還好嗎
喝不喝水
我的腳出問題了
給你
我有件事需要告訴你
[普什圖語]
怎麼了
Whoa, whoa, hey, what's going on here?
怎麼回事
What's going on?
你認出來了嗎
You recognize that face?
你應該認識
You should.
他在美軍高價值目標名單上
He's on the U.S. Military's high value target list.
葛雷姆•卡迪爾
Gholem Qadir.
販賣鴉片的大毒梟兼軍火商
Opium drug lord and arms dealer.
務必活捉
Wanted alive.
你之前說參軍的女人怎麼著來著
What were you saying about women in the military?
我們結婚的時候為什麼沒做這些有趣的事
Why didn't we do fun stuff like this when we were married?
從我們繁忙的日程中
And take time out from our
抽出時間把另一半搞瘋嗎
busy schedule of driving each other crazy?
阿曼達
Amanda.
別一副擔心的樣子  麥考斯探員
Don't look so worried, Agent Michaels.
我們都會在職業生涯的某個時間點
We've all availed ourselves
利用自己的身份來獲取一些利益
of the ostrander suite at some point in our careers.
發生了一些事  跟我一起走一趟吧
Something's come up, I'll need you to come with me.
工作來了
Duty calls.
我猜也是
Yeah, guess so.
其實
Actually...
我是指你們兩個
I meant both of you.
我們正在看的這個是什麼
What are we looking at here?
羥基環沙林  一種神經毒素
Hydroxy-cyclosarin. It's a nerve agent.
是一種化學武器的原型
It's the apocalypse in the form of a chemical weapon.
準備用於襲擊一處自由市場
And it's about to hit the open market.
是超能力聯合調查組的探員們
A.R.G.U.S. agents uncovered
在坎達格的一座製造工廠裡發現的
a manufacturing plant in Kahndaq.
幾乎所有樣本都已記錄在案  除了一個
All samples were accounted for, except for one.
這段錄影在兩周之後拍攝於
Two weeks later, this footage
庫拉克南部的一個偏僻村莊
was captured in a remote village in southern Qurac.
一毫升就能殺死方圓十英里內的生物
One milliliter has a kill radius of ten miles.
而那些樣品只需要一半就能達到同等效果
It only took half that amount to produce these results.
我們的線人追蹤到樣本
Our sources have traced the
穿越歐洲送到了馬爾科維亞的一處地方
sample through Europe to an estate in Markovia.
那就派軍隊去吧
So send in the army.
如果派軍隊  我們的政府就要面對
We send in the army, we risk an international spectacle
無法承受的國際壓力
our government can't afford.
這件事必須秘密處理
This has to be off-book.
如果你需要我起草強奪方案  沒問題
If you need me to draw up the smash and grab, done.
但約翰不是外勤探員  他沒有資格
But John isn't a field agent. He's not qualified.
就他和奧利弗•奎恩
Judging from how he and Oliver Queen
在業餘時間裡做的事而言
spend their free time,
我說他很夠格
I'd say his credits transfer.
聽著  我比你更不想
Hey, look, I don't want this
看到這件事被曝光
thing out in the open any more than you do,
但我可不會讓
but I'm not sending my
我老闆再陪著你來趟商務旅行
boss in on another one of your business trips.
這件事我不打算扯上綠箭俠
I have no intention of involving the Arrow.
我需要你
I need you.
為什麼
What for?
葛雷姆•卡迪爾
Gholem Qadir.
我們抓到過他
We caught him.
國防部幾年前把卡迪爾放了
D.O.D. turned Qadir loose a few years ago.
誰想出來的好主意
Who thought that was a good idea?
這個世界很複雜  約翰尼
It's a complicated world, Johnny.
那個神經毒素不是卡迪爾
The nerve agent's not the only WMD
唯一想經手的大規模殺傷性武器
Qadir's tried getting his scummy fingers on.
上個月  他想購買馬爾科姆•梅林的
Last month, he tried to buy Malcolm Merlyn's
地震機原型
prototype earthquake machine.
順便說一下  謝謝你阻止了他
Thank you for stopping that, by the way.
幸運的是  他不知道你也參與了那件事
Fortunately, he doesn't know about your involvement in that.
他只記得你救過他的性命
He remembers you as the man who tried to save his life.
神經毒素被鎖住了  鑰匙在
The nerve agent's under lock and key
他在馬爾科維亞的那處房產裡
at his estate in Markovia.
日程表顯示近期那裡會舉辦一場募捐活動
He's scheduled to host a fundraiser there shortly.
我們兩個人幾乎不怎麼聯繫
The two of us haven't exactly kept in touch.
這個我們來搞定  但是時機稍縱即逝
We've got that covered, but our window is rapidly closing.
好吧
OK.
那我去潛入募捐場地  把東西帶出來
So I infiltrate the fundraiser, come out with the package.
聽起來挺簡單的
Sounds simple enough.
我們這行沒什麼是簡單的
Nothing in this business is simple.
你知道的  狄格爾先生
You know that, Mr. Diggle.
跟我來
Follow me.
我不需要你的幫助就能把毒劑帶出來
I don't need you to get the nerve agent out.
我需要你把你的隊伍帶進去
I need you to get your team in.
我的隊伍
My team?
他們被稱作X特遣部隊
They're designated "Task Force X."
饒了我吧
Give me a break.
沒什麼特遣部隊
This ain't no task force.
還是這麼說吧
Let's call it like it is--
歡迎加入自殺小隊
Welcome to the suicide squad.
不只是在殘酷體罰中成長
"It's not only prisoners who grow course and hardened
並變得堅強的囚徒  還有那些
"from corporal punishment, but those as well
犯下罪行和拒絕作證的人
who perpetrate the act or who are present to witness it."
別跟他說書了
Oh, please stop giving him books.
這就是你的作戰隊伍嗎  沃勒
So this is your unit, huh, Waller?
OJ和查爾斯•曼森有事不能來了嗎
What, OJ and Charles Manson weren't available?
O•J•辛普森  斬首謀殺其妻及一男招待
查爾斯•曼森  殘殺導演波蘭斯基孕妻及朋友
這是一次危險的行動
This is a dangerous operation.
這些人都具備很有用的技能
And these men have useful skills.
任務應該有所妥協
Should the mission be compromised...
你寫下來吧
You'll just write them off.
自殺小隊
The suicide squad.
就跟他會做出犧牲似的
Yeah, like he would ever make the sacrifice.
萊拉  我不敢相信你也有份
Lyla, I can't believe you're on board with this.
那些人是殺人犯
Those men are murderers!
那奧利弗•奎恩和莎拉•蘭斯
And what's the number of bodies
又殺了多少人
between Oliver Queen and Sara Lance?
他們做的事和我做的事  完全不同
What they do, what I do, is completely different.
並不盡然  約翰  你還不明白嗎
Not really, John. Don't you see that?
我明白的是你讓殺了我哥哥的傢伙
What I see is you letting the man who killed my brother
逍遙法外
roam completely free.
不是給他自由  這是工作
It's not freedom. It's work.
這是錯誤的
It's wrong.
你們這些小可愛需要建議嗎
Do you cuties need some counseling?
我可是專業的治療師
I'm a trained therapist.
威登酒吧
"你有銷售經驗嗎"
"Do you have previous experience in retail?"
購物算嗎
Does shopping count?
莎拉
Sara?
我見過這幅表情
I've seen that look before.
當奧利進入生人勿進模式時  我在鏡子中的表情
On my face in the mirror when Ollie goes into distant mode.
堅持下去
Hang in there.
當他準備好時  會向你敞開心扉的
He'll open up to you when he's ready.
是啊  你說得沒錯
Yeah. You'd think so.
我從追蹤威爾遜先生
I started by tracing the donation
在莫伊拉競選中的捐款開始
Mr. Wilson made to Moira's campaign.
所有捐款
All of the money was
都經過了一系列的海外帳戶
routed through a series of offshore accounts.
沒有一個與本地相關聯
None of which link back to a local address,
所以我查了信用卡交易記錄
so I looked into credit card transactions
-還有汽車租賃協議  -什麼
- and car rental agreements. - What?
他肯定會以某種方式四處躲藏  但不會租汽車
He's got to get around somehow, just not by rental car.
斯萊德以前是情報科學學會的
Slade's former ASIS.
他知道如何隱藏行蹤
He knows how to be a ghost.
發生搶劫事件
Robbery in progress.
在第五大街和吉芬街處
5th and Giffen.
我們還打擊犯罪  是吧
We're still in the crime fighting business, right?
馬爾科維亞  馬爾科夫堡
藝術品拍賣會
先驅者已盯緊目標
Harbinger has eyes on the target.
點燃火把
Light the torches.
死亡射手準備就緒
Deadshot is a go.
榴散彈準備就緒
Shrapnel's a go.
老虎準備就緒
Tiger's a go.
我是知更鳥
This is Mockingbird.
先驅者  你可以隨時行動
Harbinger, you have a green light.
自由槍騎兵準備就緒了  死亡射手呢
Freelancer, you're a go. Deadshot?
自由槍騎兵在我視野中
Got Freelancer in my sights.
為什麼不朝我開槍
What's stopping you from shooting me right now?
樂意之極
Honor.
麻煩給支香煙行嗎  我的朋友
Can I trouble you for a cigarette, my friend?
我不抽煙  而且我也不是你朋友
I don't smoke, and I'm not your friend.
你知道我是誰嗎
You know who I am?
我是做什麼的嗎
What it is I do?
你販賣毒品  軍火  兒童
You're dealing drugs, weapons and children.
在戰爭中左右逢源
Play both sides of the conflict.
你的祖國深陷戰火  你還在撈錢
Make money while your country burns.
這樣的人可不止我一個
I do not have to be the only one.
放了我  我給你榮華富貴
Let me go, I make you rich.
想收買我的人嗎  卡迪爾
You trying to bribe my men, Qadir?
如果我們想賺錢
If we wanted to make a buck,
就不會來這個地方  白癡
this is the last place we'd be, moron.
趴下
Get down!
對不起  我沒有看到...
Sorry, I wasn't looking where I was--
葛雷姆•卡迪爾
Gholem Qadir.
真是不敢相信
I do know what is less likely--
約翰•狄格爾會這麼笨拙
that John Diggle would be clumsy,
世界這麼大竟然在這裡遇到你
or I would find him here, of all places.
你喜歡藝術嗎  我的朋友
You like art, my friend?
我善於抓住好的投資機會
I know a good investment when I see one.
那你是退伍了嗎
Out of the military, then?
還幹了個比較賺錢的行當
And in a more lucrative line of work.
你幹的是什麼行當呢
What kind of work is that?
一個你不應該問的行當
The kind you don't get to ask about.
很高興見到你  葛雷姆
It's good seeing you, Gholem.
一切正常嗎  狄格爾先生
Everything all right here, Mr. Diggle?
是的  他跟我一起的
Yes, he's with me.
你這個士兵現在還有護衛了
So the soldier now has his own security.
在這個行業中  若做得好  就會得罪人
In my line of work, when I do a good job, I tend to make enemies.
好人變成壞人
A good man turns bad.
壞人變成好人
Bad man turns good.
你改變了我的人生
You changed my life, you know.
相信我  那不是我本意
Trust me, that was never my intention.
我給你們的政府提供了情報
The intelligence I provided your government,
保住了我的命
it saved many lives.
現在我自由了  我會盡力做出回報
Now as a free man, I give back when I can.
當然
Of course.
趴下
Get down!
沒事了
It's all clear.
似曾相識啊  朋友
Deja vu, my friend.
卡迪爾先生
Mr. Qadir!
我沒事
I am fine.
我肯定不是目標
I do not believe I was the target.
正如我所說  當我幹得好時  就會得罪人
Like I said, when I do my job right, I tend to make enemies.
我們得走了
We should go.
幹得好  死亡射手  準備離開現場
Good job, Deadshot. You're a go for exfil.
正在離開
Already in motion.
但是
Except, uh,
不止我一個人
I'm not the only one.
榴散彈剛剛跑了
Shrapnel just bolted.
找到他
Find him.
正在跟蹤他  往東去了
Picking him up, headed east.
榴散彈
Shrapnel.
停下  返回集結點
Stand down and return to the rally point.
我不會加入你們高尚的軍隊
I won't be conscripted into your moral army.
停下  最後警告
Stand down! Final warning.
特別是在一個沒有引渡條約的國家
Especially not while in a country without an extradition treaty.
很好
Very well.
怎麼回事
What the hell's going on?
榴散彈剛剛被罰出場了
Shrapnel just fouled out of the game.
剛才怎麼回事
What the hell was that?
我們正準備為此吃爆米花慶祝呢
We're going to want popcorn for this.
約翰  你自己也說過  他們是殺人犯
You said it yourself, John. They're murderers.
是罪犯
Criminals.
他們需要激勵來聽從命令
They need an incentive to follow orders.
那你就把炸藥裝進他的頭裡嗎
So you rigged their heads with explosives?
只要他們守規矩就沒有危險
There's no danger as long as they play by the rules.
謝費爾不守規矩
Scheffer didn't.
我好像都不認識你了  萊拉
It's like I don't even know you anymore, Lyla.
卡迪爾的事現在什麼情況
Where are we at with Qadir?
救人一命  得到一枚銀星勛章
Save a man's life once, get a silver star.
救人兩命  租件晚禮服吧
Save it twice? Rent a tux.
等待您的下一步指示  長官
I'll await further instructions, sir.
葛雷姆
請光臨我的人道主義募捐會  已附詳情與說明
你的人可真難搞啊
我的耐性也不多
So is my patience.
這是你那位威爾遜先生的星城銀行帳號
This is Starling City Bank account number for your Mr. Wilson.
先說好
To be clear...
你拿走信封後我們就兩清了
take this envelope and we are through.
我對你的朋友沒興趣
I do not care who your friends are.
能達成共識嗎
別緊張  是我
Relax, it's just me.
你怎麼了  奧利
What's going on, Ollie?
你可以和我談談
Hey! Talk to me.
現在還不到時候
Now is not the time.
那要等到什麼時候
Then when is the time?
為什麼要找黑手黨  你失控了
The Bratva, Ollie? You're losing your grip.
斯萊德影響了你的判斷
Ok? Slade's getting in your head.
我想結束這一切
I need this to stop.
所以  我得找到他
And for it to stop, I need to find him.
在那之前  你覺得你
Yeah, and until then, how long do you think
一個人可以撐多久
you can keep this up for?
你不吃東西  很少休息
You're not eating, you're barely sleeping.
只要睡下就會做噩夢
And when you do, you have nightmares.
你夢到她了  是不是
They're about her, aren't they?
看著我
Hey, look at me.
你已經盡力了
You did what you had to do, ok?
艾沃當時差點殺死了我們兩個
Ivo was going to shoot Shado, or me, or both of us.
那是不可能的選擇
It was an impossible choice.
但我選了
I made it, anyway.
但如果你沒那麼選
But if you had chosen differently,
那你每晚夢到的將會是我
then it would be me haunting you at night.
你現在也有危險  莎拉
It still could be, Sara.
所以我們得分開
That's why we have to stop.
你什麼意思
What are you saying?
他會利用你傷害我
He's going to use you to hurt me.
或直接攻擊你
Or he's going to hurt you...
跟我保持距離
Stay away from me.
既然你還沒有提起
Seeing as how you haven't brought it up,
據我分析  我給你的線索裡
I'm guessing you haven't got very far
你並沒有查到什麼
with that H.I.V.E. Lead I gave you.
少廢話  做你的事
Just make this quick.
你還是這麼健談  約翰
You're usually so chatty, John.
是女人的問題嗎  她騙到你了嗎
These problems with your girl, they got you down, huh?
那你的女兒呢
And what about your girl?
你在牢裡供起來的那個
The one you have a shrine to in that cell of yours?
佐伊
Zoe.
你女兒知道你是做什麼的嗎
Does your daughter know what you do for a living?
她就是我做這行的原因
She is why I do what I do.
-真的嗎  -對
- Really? - Yeah.
一個小女孩能有多少敵人
How many enemies can a little girl have?
我不知道
I wouldn't know.
我花不掉的酬勞
Everything I make beyond expenses
都匯進了一個保密信託
goes in a blind trust.
女孩最想要的是爸爸
A girl needs her father.
不會是我這個爸爸
Nah, not this father.
我唯一能為她做的
Best thing I can do for her life...
就是不參與她的人生
not be in it.
好了嗎
Is it ready?
我們花了好大力氣才給約翰
You know, we went through all that trouble to get Johnny here
搞到這個破舞會的邀請函
invited to this little shindig.
不用就太可惜了
Seems like an awful waste not to use that invitation.
你來用  一旦神經藥劑得手
You're using it. Once you have hands on the nerve agent,
就放進口袋走人
pocket it, walk right on out.
遵命
Copy that.
非常感謝您的傾情贊助
Thank you very much. Your generosity is much appreciated.
雖然這身不是迷彩服
That's not exactly army camo.
可你想過萬一卡迪爾認出你該怎麼辦嗎
But have you given any thought to what would happen if Qadir recognizes you anyway?
狄格先生  這是哪位美人啊
Mr. Diggle. Who is this vision?
他的新保鏢
His new bodyguard.
那你可得給我介紹下你的保安公司了
Mmm. You will have to refer me to your security company.
很高興你今晚能前來
I'm glad you could come tonight.
這遠不足以報答你對我的兩次
It's the least I could do after you saved my life.
救命之恩
Again.
我們裡面見  夥計
I will see you inside, my friend.
葛雷姆
Gholem.
我似乎沒來得及
It would seem I didn't have time
幫我的保鏢辦理邀請函
to get credentials for my associate.
來  跟我一起
Come. This way.
我很抱歉
Gosh, I'm so sorry.
我忘記還有這個了
I forgot those were in there.
盡情享受  狄格先生
Enjoy the benefit, Mr. Diggle.
死亡射手和裝備都到位了
Deadshot and his gear are in position.
老虎總攬全域
Tiger's got the overwatch.
全體注意  準備行動
Harbinger to all, fire in the hole.
十點鐘方向有敵人
Shooter at my ten!
我掩護你
I got you covered!
好  快上
Bounding! Go go go!
全殲
All clear!
還是個孩子
It's just a kid.
你今晚真漂亮
And don't you look lovely tonight?
謝謝
Appreciate it.
我覺得你應該和你的保鏢跳支舞
Oh, I think you owe your bodyguard a dance.
請吧
I insist.
死亡射手正在前去取包裹
Deadshot en route to package.
世界的命運
The fate of the world
落在佛洛德•羅通手上
resting in the hands of Floyd Lawton.
這有利於任務
It helps to focus on the mission.
你就是這麼麻痹自己的嗎
Is that what you tell yourself?
我不會以扭曲的眼光
I tell myself to see the world how it is,
看待這個世界
not how I want to see it.
我們都行走在灰色地帶
We both operate in the grey.
唯一的差別就是  我願意承認
The only difference is, is I'm willing to admit it.
那不是我們兩個唯一的差別
That's not the only difference between us.
你說得對  但我不喜歡評判別人
That's true. I don't judge other people for it.
萊拉  我還是原來的那個我
Lyla, I'm the same man I've always been.
我也沒有變啊
And I'm who I've always been.
你太固執了  約翰
You're rigid, John.
你不接受任何其他人的看法
You're blind to any viewpoint that isn't yours.
過去的幾個月很開心
These past few months have been amazing.
但我們一直沉溺玩樂  而非交流
But we've done more playing than talking.
因為我們一旦開始談  就會鬧分手
Because when we talk, we tend to get divorced.
威登酒吧
別擔心
Don't worry.
這是我第一次做
It's virgin.
所以它嘗起來才那麼糟嗎
Ugh. Which is why it tastes terrible.
是啊
True.
所以
So.
看來你和莎拉進展不錯
It looks like things with you and Sara are going well.
我覺得這個話題不該和你談
I'm not sure you're the best person to talk to with all this.
為什麼
And why is that?
是因為出軌  沉船  溺水
Is it because of the whole cheating, shipwreck, drowning,
沒淹死  你回來了  她也回來了這事嗎
not drowning, you're back, she's back thing?
抱歉
Sorry.
我說得很殘忍但也很誠實
It's brutal AA honesty talking.
我想我更喜歡我們相互欺騙的時候
I think I preferred it when we were all lying to each other.
不  你只是覺得你喜歡
No, you just thought you did.
我幾乎比所有人都瞭解你  奧利
I know you better than almost anyone, Ollie.
我知道你覺得自己不配得到幸福
I know that you think that you don't deserve to be happy,
但你錯了
but you're wrong.
你或許認為跟她保持一定距離
You may think that keeping her at arm's length,
是在保護她  但其實並不是
you're protecting her, but you're not.
你只是在保護自己
You're only protecting yourself.
不是那麼簡單
It's more complicated than that.
從來都不簡單
It always is.
我查到你給我的那銀行帳戶的地址了
I got the address for that account number you gave me.
我來叫羅伊和莎拉
I'll call Roy and Sara.
不  我不會讓斯萊德有更多目標
No. I'm not giving Slade any more targets.
你不能隻身前往  那是自殺
You can't go out there by yourself, it's suicide.
這事由我們兩人而起
This started with the two of us.
也要結束於我們兩人之間
That's how it ends.
死亡射手已就位
Deadshot's on target.
找到了
Bingo.
我不知道該怎麼辦
I don't know what to do.
他領先太多了
He's too far ahead.
他花了好多年計劃這一切
I mean, he spent years planning this,
而且他知道有關我的一切
and he knows everything about me.
我不能  我...
I can't, I...
我不知道怎麼阻止他
I don't know how to stop him.
你可以讓別人幫你
Well, you start by letting people help you.
但他會來對付你的
But he's going to come after you.
你之所以活著...
You're alive...
是因為莎朵死了
because Shado isn't.
等他來的時候  你覺得我們倆在不在一起
And when he does, do you think it'll make a difference
會有區別嗎
whether or not we're together?
讓他來吧
Let him come.
我不再是他在島上認識的那個小女孩了
I'm not the girl he knew on the island.
我沒那麼容易被殺死的
I'm not that easy to kill.
一起面對
Together?
Together.
我進來了
I'm in.
30秒後神經毒劑到手
I'll have the nerve agent in my pocket in 30 seconds.
先驅者
Harbinger...
我這裡出了一點小狀況
We've got what I would describe as a little bit of a situation here.
解釋清楚
Explain.
我看到神經毒劑了
Well, I got eyes on the nerve agent,
但我無法移動它
and I'm not going to be able to move it,
更不用直接拿走了
much less pocket it.
原地待命  死亡射手  我要跟沃勒匯報一下
Stand by, Deadshot. I need to talk to Waller.
知更鳥  請說
Go for Mockingbird.
我們遇到麻煩了
We have a situation.
目標比行動前指示的大很多
The package is much bigger than our pre-op briefing indicated.
原地待命
Stand by.
死亡射手已就位  我需要看到他所看到的
Deadshot's on target; I need to see what he does.
啟動他眼裡的攝像頭
Activate the camera in his eye piece.
羅通裝備的多光譜視頻
Multi spectrum from Lawton's rig
馬上出現
coming in...now.
相符
It's a match.
老虎  準備撤退
Tiger, move for extraction.
死亡射手  原地不動
Deadshot, remain in position.
先驅者和自由槍騎兵  撤退到集合點
Harbinger and Freelancer, evac and head to the rally point.
死亡射手還沒有帶著東西上來
Deadshot still isn't topside with the package.
我只是需要看到罷了  撤到集合點
I only needed eyes on. Fall back to the rally point.
等等  你早知道神經毒劑太大不能帶走嗎
Wait...you knew that the nerve agent was too large to be extracted?
撤退到集合點
Fall back to the rally point.
九號已準備好
Nine is inbound and hot.
知更鳥撤出
Mockingbird out.
九號是什麼
What the hell are Nines?
MQ九號  劫掠者
Mq-9s. Predators.
沃勒發動了無人機襲擊
Waller's called in a drone strike.
十分鐘之內  這裡的所有人都會死
Everyone here is dead inside of ten minutes.
九號裝載著地獄火導彈
The Nines carry the hellfire missile.
只要一枚就足以把這棟大樓夷為平地
Just one of them can level this whole building.
你老闆不在乎會把誰炸死
And your boss doesn't care who's here when it does.
萊拉  我們得把這些人弄出去
Lyla, we have to get these people out of here.
或許我們可以啟動房屋警報
Maybe there's a house alarm we can trigger.
約翰  我們必須要走了
John, we have to move now.
我有個更好的主意
I have a better idea.
打擾一下
Excuse me.
請大家注意
Can I have your attention, please?
感謝我們的主辦人
In honor of our host.
葛雷姆•卡迪爾擅長做一切他決心要做的事
Gholem Qadir excels at everything he puts his mind to,
生意
be it business,
慈善
philanthropy...
或者恐怖主義事業
or terrorism.
我覺得葛雷姆是一個文藝復興式的人物
Yeah, I guess you could say gholem is somewhat of a renaissance man.
他在每個領域都涉足一點
He dabbles in a little bit of everything.
比如說軍火交易  我說性交易了嗎
Like arms trading-- did I mention the sex trafficking?
還有他手裡的致命神經毒劑
Or the deadly nerve agent that he's holding
就在這舞池下面10米的地方
just 30 feet beneath this very dance floor.
這都是謊話  這個人是雇傭兵
These are lies! This man is a mercenary!
勞頓
Lawton!
他沒有回答  我得去幫他
He's not answering. I have to go help him.
我真不敢相信我剛說了這些
I can't believe I just said that.
你  你五年前也在阿富汗
You! You were in Afghanistan five years ago.
你和那個叛徒從一開始就在騙我
You and that Judas have been deceiving me from the start.
來得正好
Good timing.
我的邀請涵遲遲不來  等煩了
Got tired of waiting for my invitation.
違抗命令了啊  約翰
Disobeying orders, John.
小心身後
Behind you.
你欠我兩個人情了
That's two you owe me, junior.
我們得走了
We have to go.
沃勒讓我待在這裡
Waller told me to stay here.
無人機馬上就會來襲了
There's an incoming drone strike.
真及時  讓你的隊員都出去
How contemporary. Get your team clear.
你就是我的隊員之一
You are on my team.
你該離開了
And it's time for you to go.
是啊  說得對  是時候了
Yeah, that's right. It is time.
這就是我離開的方式
And this is my way to go.
自殺小隊  記得嗎
Suicide squad, remember?
我可有可無  約翰
I'm expendable, John.
我腦中那顆該死的炸彈也能證明這一點
Even got the damn bomb in my head to prove it.
這樣  我至少做了件光榮的事
This way, at least I get to go out doing something honorable.
你不能死得這麼容易  羅通
You don't get to die that easy, Lawton.
是嗎
Really?
那你給我一個
Why don't you give me even just
不這麼做的理由
one good reason why not, huh?
佐伊
Zoe.
-那神經毒氣怎麼辦  -相信我
- What about the nerve gas? - Believe me--
沃勒已經都搞定了
Waller's already got that covered.
快走  快快快
Go, go, go, go, go, go, go!
無人機改變飛行路線了  現在正跟著我們
The drone shifted course. It's following us.
你覺得很好笑嗎
Do you find that funny?
那個女人真厲害啊
Whoa. What a woman.
你們覺得她是怎麼知道把無人機派去哪裡的
How do you think she knew where to send the drone, huh?
我是說確切的坐標地點
And I mean, the precise coordinates.
-移植追蹤器  -炸彈和GPS
- The implants. - Bomb and GPS.
很聰明對吧
Pretty clever, right?
無人機的目標不是葛雷姆的房子
The drone ain't targeting Gholem's house.
而是我
It's targeting me.
等等  不該先問問我的意見嗎
Whoa, hang on, do I get a say in this?
-轉身  -你幹什麼
- Turn around. - What are you doing?
我寧願被炸飛
Look, I think I'd rather get blown up!
穩住  會很疼的
Hold still. This is going to hurt.
馬爾科夫政府威脅說要報復
The Markovian government is threatening retaliation
在禁飛區無緣無故出動無人機襲擊
following an unprovoked drone attack over a no-fly zone.
我們不就是想避免這種局面嗎  做得漂亮啊
Just the attention we wanted to avoid. Well done.
又不是我派無人機去的
I'm not the one who sent that drone.
無人機隱身了  化學武器藏匿點
It was cloaked. An explosion atop
上面的爆炸是很容易解釋的
a chemical weapons cache is easy to explain.
可是  還有目擊者  所以我們
Instead, there were witnesses and we had
還得派海豹突擊隊去清理現場
to send in a seal team to clean out the estate.
我覺得你拉我幫你幹什麼不幹凈的勾當時
I guess you'll think twice before dragging me
就應該三思而後行  沃勒
in to do your dirty work, Waller.
我並不覺得這是個問題
Somehow I don't think it will be an issue.
就這樣  狄格爾先生
Good day, Mr. Diggle.
不可思議啊
Kind of uncanny.
狄格爾怎麼知道羅通的追蹤器在什麼地方
How Diggle knew exactly where Lawton's implant was.
總之
Still,
這暴露出了一個明顯的設計缺陷
it exposed an obvious design flaw.
以後把追蹤器植入到脊椎裡吧
We'll be putting in the implants in their spinal vertebrae now.
讓羅通跟其他人準備手術
Have Lawton and the others prepped for surgery.
沃勒說幾年後你可能會得到赦免
Waller said in a few years, you might even get a pardon.
不用擔心  約翰
Don't worry, John.
我不會活那麼久的  你我心知肚明
We both know I'm not going to be around that long.
沒被解雇嗎
You still employed?
我這種權限級別的人沒那麼容易
People with my security clearance aren't that easy
-就擺脫的  -對
- to get rid of. - Right.
那我們呢  約翰
What about us, Johnny?
昨晚殺我弟弟的那個人
Last night, the man who killed my brother
比要保護全世界的那個女人
showed more character than the woman charged
更加高尚
with protecting the world.
是非好壞的界限已經沒那麼明顯了
Good and bad is not so clear to me.
但是有一件事我非常確定
One thing I do know for sure,
黑白分明那麼確定
black and white...
就是我不能再失去你了
is that I can't ever lose you again.
終於
Finally.
我們也達成一致了
Something we agree on.
又多了一個原先是恐怖分子的盟友
Well, there goes another terrorist-turned-ally.
對了  我推薦你
By the way, I put you in for a commendation
去救卡迪爾了
for saving Qadir's ass.
記得請我喝酒
You owe me a beer.
恭喜
Congratulations.
是啊  殺個孩子得到勛章  對吧
Yeah, well, kill a kid, get a medal, right?
要是那個人拿卡拉希步槍朝你射擊
When someone's shooting a kalishnikov at you,
那他就不是個孩子
he's not a kid.
我不這麼認為
I see things differently.
世界很複雜  約翰
It's a complicated world, Johnny.
我可以叫你約翰嗎
Is it OK if I call you Johnny?
我好像還不知道你的名字  麥考斯
I don't think I caught your first name, Michaels.
萊拉
Lyla.
真的很高興認識你  萊拉
It's really good to meet you, Lyla.
下面是國際新聞  一支聯合國巡查隊
In international news, a United Nations inspections team
因為藏在人道主義者葛雷姆•卡迪爾
was called to a chemical weapons manufacturing facility
馬爾科夫莊園下的
hidden beneath the Markovian estate
化學武器生產製造設施而出動
of humanitarian Gholem Qadir.
星城新聞  市長候選人莫伊拉•奎恩
Closer to home, mayoral candidate Moira Queen
在各地進行演說
stumped for an initiative
企圖在學校游泳池建造項目後再復興市中心
to revive inner city after school swim programs.
我記得自己的孩子小時候
Oh, I remember how much my children
有多麼喜歡游泳
enjoyed swimming when they were young.
他們在泳池里拉都拉不出來
I couldn't get them out of the pool.
我們需要...
We need--
我還以為你不喜歡游泳
I thought you hated swimming.
我恨游泳
I detest swimming.
西婭也是
So does Thea.
有時候我母親
My mother sometimes--ahem--
不是那麼喜歡真相
enjoys a casual relationship with the truth.
總之
Anyway.
謝謝你在這裡陪我
Thank you for being there for me.
你是說不讓你把我推開嗎
You mean for not letting you push me away?
我不會再那樣了
I'm going to stop doing that.
是嗎  那就好
Yeah? Good.
反正你也是在浪費自己的時間
You'll be wasting your time, anyways.
好像你聽從我的建議了
It looks like you took my advice.
謝謝你
Thank you.
幫我跟莎拉
Helping me with Sara,
我知道  這樣做不容易
I know that that... can't be easy.
幫兩個我在乎的人嗎
Helping two people I care about?
沒有比這更容易的事了
There's nothing easier.
我是來帶莎拉去吃飯的
I came by to take Sara to dinner.
你想一起去吃嗎
Would you care to join?
我很想去  但是得先去見個老朋友
I'd love to, but I need to go see an old friend.
好吧
OK.
你好  奧利弗
Hello, Oliver.
你好  阿曼達
Hello, Amanda.
還生我的氣嗎
Still mad at me?
算你走運  你不在我的名單之上了
Lucky for you, You've been pushed down that list.
真的嗎  跟我相比你更加想殺的人是誰
Really? Who do you want to kill more than me?
斯萊德•威爾遜還活著
Slade Wilson is alive.
你把他殺了
You killed him.
不可能還活著的
It's not possible.
只要跟斯萊德有關  一切皆有可能
Everything is possible where Slade is concerned.
我需要你幫我找到他
And I need your help to find him.
-我可能有線索  -什麼線索
- I might have something. - What?
我們一直追蹤的一個人  是個雇傭兵
There's a new player we've been tracking-- mercenary.
他所到之處屍體遍地
He's left a trail of bodies
從澳門到伊斯坦布爾再到里斯本
from Macau to Istanbul to Lisbon.
最後到了星城
A trail that leads right here to Starling.
我們一直叫他喪鐘
We've been calling him Deathstroke.